Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
- Office Employees International Union (OEIU), Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Office Employees News, 1947; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.3, no.8 (Mar. 1947)
  - Item 10: Office unionism by Paul R. Hutchings, 1950; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Office workers look at their trade by Paul R. Hutchings, 1947; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: The first report of the District #1 Salaried Div., 1955; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: What about white collar wages? A conference (sponsored by New Jersey Local Unions, Office Employees International Union AFL), 1951; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Developing and maintaining an active union - third annual fall conference, 1952; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: What about white collar wages ? Summary of a conference, 1951; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Organizational techniques and procedures, 1954; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Secretary-treasurer's handbook, 1950; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Collective bargaining guide and model agreement, 1954; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Office Employees Insurance Trust Fund of California, 1957; Publication (Box 284, Folder 3)
- Office Employees International Union (OEIU), Publication (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Organizational techniques and procedures, 1959; Publication (Box 284, Folder 4)
- Office Employees International Union (OEIU), Publication (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Pen Pusher, 1947; Publication (Box 285, Folder 1)
    Notes: Aug-Dec 1947
  - Item 2: The Pen Pusher, 1948; Publication (Box 285, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb-Mar 1948
  - Item 3: The Pen Pusher, 1948; Publication (Box 285, Folder 1)
    Notes: July-Aug 1948
  - Item 4: Pen pushers' notes, Publication (Box 285, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 7-8, 10
  - Item 5: Pen pushers' notes, Publication (Box 285, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 2-4, 7, 9
  - Item 6: Pen pushers' notes, Publication (Box 285, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 5, no. 1-4, 7-11
  - Item 7: Pen pushers' notes, Publication (Box 285, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 6, no. 1-2, 4, 6-8, 10-12
- Office Employees International Union (OEIU), Publication (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Are you confronted with job evaluation?, 1947; Publication (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Presidents report to the 1949 Convention, Publication (Box 285, Folder 2)
- Office Employees International Union (OEIU), Publication (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Women in the working force, Publication (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Paper Industry Study (1960), Comparative Analysis of OEIU agreements, Publication (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Survey of Utility Companies, 1960; Publication (Box 285, Folder 3)
- Office Employees International Union (OEIU), Publication (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Secretary-treasurer's handbook, 1950; Publication (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: You and unions, 1951; Publication (Box 285, Folder 4)
    Author: Dale Yoder; Phelan
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: How Amalgamated Locals work, organizationfinanceselectionsservices., Publication (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Democracy in action (the Oil, chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Legislative Conference, Washington, D.C., June 4-5-6, 1964), Publication (Box 286, Folder 1)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: OWIU historical highlights, Publication (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Intl. Union, AFL-CIO/CLC, 1977; Publication (Box 286, Folder 2)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Facts and Trends, 1957; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 10
  - Item 2: correspondence, 1956; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Supporting data for 1957 wage program, Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Plain talk on racial tension, 1956; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: How to run a clean union, 1957; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: International Oil Worker, 1934; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 5, no. 21 (1934)
  - Item 7: A plan of group insurance, 1957; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Your union dues, 1959; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Scholarship program, 1959; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Your pipe line to security, 1957; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Stewards Grievance guide, 1956; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Resolutions adopted., 1956; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Resolution of procedure and constitution, 1954; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Fact Book, 1955; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Fact Book, 1956; Publication (Box 286, Folder 3)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: OCAW energy policy: adopted May 10, 1977, Publication (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Steward's grievance guide, 1956; Publication (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: OCAW National oil bargaining policy, 1977-1978: a program for Union building through collective bargaining, Publication (Box 286, Folder 4)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: O.C.A.W. Canadian oil bargaining policy, 1969, Publication (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: O.C.A.W. oil bargaining policy, 1966, Publication (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: A position paper on cost of living escalators: summary, 1974; Publication (Box 286, Folder 5)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Handbook for OCAW women, 1973; Publication (Box 286, Folder 6)
    Author: Katherine Stone
  - Item 2: The OCAW plan, a ten-point program for peaceful use of atomic energy, Publication (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: You're invited, Publication (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Your union dues, 1960; Publication (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, 1960; Publication (Box 286, Folder 6)
    Author: Harry Seligson
  - Item 6: Union Carbide, 1968; Publication (Box 286, Folder 6)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Fact Book, 1955; Publication (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Fact Book, 1960; Publication (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Fact Book, 1972; Publication (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Fact Book, 1965; Publication (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: The public interest in oil labor negotiations: a report, 1966; Publication (Box 286, Folder 7)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Union dues where they go and what they buy, Publication (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Research and Education Dept., 1954; Publication (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Research and Education Dept., 1955; Publication (Box 286, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 2 no.1- 7
  - Item 4: Research and Education Dept., 1956; Publication (Box 286, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 3, no.1-3, 5
  - Item 5: Survey of fringe benefits in OWIU-CIO contracts as at May 1, 1953, Publication (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Survey of key refinery wage rates as of Oct. 15, 1953, Publication (Box 286, Folder 8)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Facts & Trends, 1955; Publication (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Facts & Trends, 1961; Publication (Box 286, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 8
  - Item 3: Educational program of the Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1954; Publication (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Survey of refinery wage rates as of Sept. 1, 1959, Publication (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Research Bulletin, 1971; Publication (Box 286, Folder 9)
    Notes: Oct. 1971
  - Item 6: Discussion leaders manual (free to OWIU Locals holding Leadership Training Courses), Publication (Box 286, Folder 9)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The public interest in oil labor negotiations: a report, 1966; Publication (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Steward's grievance guide, 1956; Publication (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: OCAW National oil bargaining policy; 1977-1978., Publication (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: O.C.A.W. National oil bargaining policy; 1973-1974, 1972; Publication (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: O.C.A.W. oil bargaining policy; 1968, Publication (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: O.C.A.W. oil bargaining policy; 1971-1972, 1970; Publication (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: O.C.A.W. Steward's guide, Publication (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: International Policies of the Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO., 1956; Publication (Box 286, Folder 10)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: OCAW Union industry pension fund, 1965; Publication (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Unity is strength, OCAW participation in local-regional, national and international labor organizations, Publication (Box 287, Folder 1)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: O.C.A.W. national oil bargaining policy; 1975-1977., 1974; Publication (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Key economic indicators general economy and chemical and allied products industries, 1972; Publication (Box 287, Folder 2)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: International structure and how it operates in a Democratic Union (workshop matl.), Publication (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: O.C.A.W. Canadian oil bargaining policy; 1969., Publication (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: OCAW Preliminary data for Canadian Oil Bargaining Conference, 1968; Publication (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: A profile of Union Carbide Corporation, 1969; Publication (Box 287, Folder 3)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Workshop matl. - Leadership, its discovery; The membership an analysis; The instructor's approach to planning; Educational programs and how to apply; Union meetings and how to make them; The local union its purpose, Publication (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Discussion leaders manual (free to OWIU Locals holding Leadership Training Courses), Publication (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Analysis U.S. Chemical and Allied Products Industries, 1967; Publication (Box 287, Folder 4)
    Author: Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union. Research Dept.
  - Item 4: Pensions and collective bargaining, 1964; Publication (Box 287, Folder 4)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Fact book, 1976; Publication (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Analysis and recommendations pension plans, nineteen major oil companies, 1966; Publication (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Economics for working Canadians, 1977; Publication (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Structure of the Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Your union meeting, Publication (Box 287, Folder 5)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Gulfport News, 1954; Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb-May (1954)
  - Item 2: The Gulfport News, 1955; Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan-Feb (1955)
  - Item 3: Report of Oil Workers Committee on Local 688's participation program, 1952; Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: From: Local 513, Oil Workers Union, CIO -- To: The Union Carbide and Carbon Chemical Company, Whiting, Indiana -- Subject: Wage proposals, 1948; Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Minutes of meeting between Gulf Oil Corporation and the Oil Workers International Union, Local No. 651, 1954; Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The movement to organize the International Association of Oil Field, Gas Well and Refinery Workers of America., 1937; Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Financial analysis of thirty-eight oil companies: 1939-1951, 1952; Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The case against Carbide, Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The Road we travel, 1948; Publication (Box 288, Folder 1)
- Oil Workers International Union (OWIU), Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Oil Industry - Recommendations of fact-finding board, 1946; Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Special News Letter No. 101, Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Strike News, 1939; Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
    Notes: no. 104 (Nov.4, 1939)
  - Item 4: Bulletin no. 112, 1940; Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: CIO Oil Workers on strike against Mid-Continent Petroleum Corporation, 1939; Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Research and Education Dept., 1954; Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 3-4, 6
  - Item 7: Leadership Training Institute - Teacher's Manual, 1948; Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Wage rates - Effective - March 1, 1951, Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Les Ouvriers de Petrole, 1952; Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
    Language: French.
  - Item 10: So you're now a member of OWIU, 1945; Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: The working people of Europe, Publication (Box 288, Folder 2)
- Oil Workers International Union (OWIU), Publication (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bargaining policy statement - by CIO's Oil Workers, 1953; Publication (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Individual Annual Reports of the Executive Council, 1946; Publication (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Financial Report. June 1, 1948 - May 31, 1949, 1948-1949 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Why; the oil workers' case for wage adjustments, 1946; Publication (Box 288, Folder 3)
- Oil Workers International Union (OWIU), Publication (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Your dues dollar, 1945; Publication (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Research and Education Dept. - #0-89, 1947; Publication (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Guide for handling grievances, 1946; Publication (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining for pipeline workers, 1945; Publication (Box 288, Folder 4)
- Oil Workers International Union (OWIU), Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1948; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Press Release, 1945; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Financial Statement of T.M. McCormick, 1948; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The Steward Knows, Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Comic strip - "From Adam to Atom", 1951; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The working people of Europe, Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: So you're now a member of OWIU, 1945; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Guide for handling grievances, 1946; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: International policies, 1946; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: You and your union, 1946; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Is it fair?, 1947; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: A union busting plan, oil trust style, 1949; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Why do pure oil workers have so much employer trouble there must be a reason, 1947; Publication (Box 288, Folder 5)
- Oil Workers International Union (OWIU), Publication (Box 288, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: In the matter of Ashland Oil & Refining Co. et al and Oil Workers International Union - wage dispute, 1945; Publication (Box 288, Folder 6)
    Author: U.S. Dept. of Labor
  - Item 2: The Oil Panel was appointed by the Secretary of Labor., 1945; Publication (Box 288, Folder 6)
- Oil Workers International Union (OWIU), Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Facts & Trends, 1955; Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 1- 4
  - Item 2: Facts & Trends, 1956; Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 2, no.1-3, 5- 6
  - Item 3: Research and Education Dept., 1951-1952 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 1, no.2-13
  - Item 4: Research and Education Dept., 1952-1953 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 2, no.1, 3-4
  - Item 5: Research and Education Dept., 1953-1954 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 3, no.1-6
  - Item 6: Still more Social Security for you, 1954; Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Survey of key refinery wage rates as of Oct. 15, 1953, Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Financial facts about twenty four oil companies, 1952-1953 (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: The instructor's approach to planning and presenting training programs, 1954; Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
    Author: Oil Workers' International Union. Research and Education Dept.
  - Item 10: Petroleum prices - 1946-1947, Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Production is up! Profits are up!, 1951; Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: How to speak at union meetings.., Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: The church speaks for labor, 1951; Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Educational program of the Oil Workers International Union, Publication (Box 288, Folder 7)
- Oil Workers International Union (OWIU), Publication (Box 288, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Your union dues, 1954; Publication (Box 288, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Flow of union dues and services, Publication (Box 288, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Stewards manual, Publication (Box 288, Folder 8)
    Author: Oil Workers International Union. Research and Education Dept.
  - Item 4: Local union secretary: guide and manual, 1947; Publication (Box 288, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Structure of the Oil Workers International Union, CIO, Publication (Box 288, Folder 8)
- One Big Union, Publication (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: One big union of the wage workers, 1919; Publication (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: One Big Union - Official Bulletin no. 8, 1920; Publication (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: One Big Union, 1920; Publication (Box 289, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 1, no.50
- National Optical Workers, Publication (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: News Letter, 1955-1959 (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Second Annual Optical Worker National Conference - Minutes, 1954; Publication (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Minutes of the Fourth Annual Meeting, 1956; Publication (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Minutes of Executive Board Meeting, 1956; Publication (Box 289, Folder 2)
- National Optical Workers, Publication (Box 289, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Optical Bulletin, 1946; Publication (Box 289, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 6, no. 12
  - Item 2: Optical Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 289, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 7, no. 1, 3-6, 8-10
  - Item 3: Optical Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 289, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 8, no.3-5, 7, 9-12
  - Item 4: Optical Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 289, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 9, no. 2, 6, 8-9, 11
  - Item 5: Optical Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 289, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 10, no. 1
- National Optical Workers, Publication (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Optical Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 289, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 9, no. 7
  - Item 2: Optical Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 289, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 10, no. 11-12
  - Item 3: Optical Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 289, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 11, no.1-3, 5, 7-10, 12
  - Item 4: Optical Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 289, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 12, no. 2-5
- Oregon State Employees Association, Publication (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-laws, 1976; Publication (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining in state employment: Oregon's experience, 1966; Publication (Box 289, Folder 5)
    Author: Thomas C. Enright
- International Union of Operating Engineers, Publication (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A training course developed in cooperation with the Department of Organization, Research and Education // Leadership Training, Publication (Box 289, Folder 6)
- International Union of Operating Engineers, Publication (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Decisions and Opinions of the General President29th Convention, 1972; Publication (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Minutes of the General Executive Board29th Convention, 1972; Publication (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Training, 1969; Publication (Box 289, Folder 7)
- Pacific Coast School for Workers (Berkeley, Calif.), Publication (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Reports by staff members, officers and committees to the annual meeting., 1939; Publication (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Reports by staff members, officers and committees to the annual meeting., 1940; Publication (Box 290, Folder 1)
- Pacific Coast School for Workers (Berkeley, Calif.), Publication (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Yearbook, 1941; Publication (Box 290, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 9, 1941
  - Item 2: Special problems in workers' education as related to the war and national defense, 1942; Publication (Box 290, Folder 2)
    Author: George Hedley
- Pacific Coast School for Workers (Berkeley, Calif.), Publication (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Labor Institute at the Ninth Annual Summer Session, 1941; Publication (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Yearbook of the Ninth Annual Summer Session, 1941; Publication (Box 290, Folder 3)
- United Packinghouse Workers of America (UPWA), Publication (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of Public Review Advisory Commission of United Packinghouse, Food, and Allied Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1961; Publication (Box 291, Folder 1)
- United Packinghouse Workers of America (UPWA), Publication (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Testimony at hearings on proposed International Trade Organization Charter, 1947; Publication (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: A report to the Automation Fund Committee, 1963; Publication (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The UPWA's program against poverty: produced for the 15th Constitutional Convention, United Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers, AFL-CIO, May 16-20, 1966, Los Angeles, California, Publication (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Progress report, Automation Committee, formed under agreements of September 1, 1959 between Armour and Company and United Packinghouse Food and Allied Workers, Publication (Box 291, Folder 2)
- United Packinghouse Workers of America (UPWA), Publication (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: In the matter of the arbitration between Boston Sausage and Provision Company, Inc. and United Packinghouse Workers of America - Memorandum opinion of arbitrator, Publication (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: In the arbitration between: The Utah Ice and Storage Company and United Packinghouse Workers of America: Report and decision of arbitrator, Publication (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: United States of America before the national labor Board Meat packing Commission., Publication (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: District Six Council - 20th Anniversary, 1964; Publication (Box 291, Folder 3)
- United Packinghouse Workers of America (UPWA), Publication (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Film guide, 1950; Publication (Box 291, Folder 4)
    Author: United Packinghouse Workers of America. Education Dept.
  - Item 2: Immediate Release - 'An offer to provide skilled labor to slaughter livestock in order to provide market outlets for the farmers.', 1948; Publication (Box 291, Folder 4)